<resources>
    <string name="app_name">AboutCitrus</string>
    <string name="action_channel">Channel</string>

    <string name="citrus_url">https://plus.google.com/communities/110928715574226998482</string>
    <string name="citrus_github">https://github.com/Citrus-CAF</string>
    <string name="citrus_channel">https://telegram.me/TheCitrusChannel</string>

    <string name="founder">Founder/Developer</string>
    <string name="developer">Developer</string>
    <string name="maintainer">Maintainer</string>

    <string name="adarshmr">Adarsh MR</string>
    <string name="adarshmr_url">https://plus.google.com/+AdarshMR1</string>
    <string name="rohit">Rohit Poroli</string>
    <string name="rohit_url">https://plus.google.com/+RohitPoroli</string>

    <string name="about_citrus">Citrus-CAF, unlike the name suggests, was initially based off CyanogenMod,
        in the early days of Marshmallow, we even had another name at that point. Later, taking into consideration
        feedbacks of the very first slew of testers and carefully studying the needs and demands of our users, we
        rebased the project to Code Aurora Sources, more commonly known as CAF. Time went by and Nougat released,
        and we decided that it was time, Citrus-CAF had to see the daylight. We rebased everything to the brank
        spanking Nougat released. Later we realized the true potential of CAF tags, how each of them altered the
        device performance on different SOCs. After a lot of thinking, we decided to keep different sources for
        difference SOCs in our git and hours of debugging later, the Xiaomi Redmi Note 3 was the first device to
        get a taste of our Tangy Nougat. In the beginning, it was just two people behind , but in time, a lot of
        people joined us, as each giving their own contibutions.</string>

    <string name="about_citrus2">Citrus-CAF was built to create an amazing combination of customization, performance
        and most of the demanded features by our users, whereas we\'ve Cardinal, to deliver minimal customizations, but
        the greatest stability!</string>

    <string name="about_citrus3"> When Birds Fly!</string>
</resources>
